In the last lecture we made sure that we can also remove ingredients from the burger, now I want to update
W ostatnim wykadzie upewnilimy si, e moemy rwnie usuwa skadniki z burgera,
the burger price and display it as part of that burger too.
wiedzc, kiedy zaktualizowa cen burgera i wywietli go jako cz tego burgera.
Now actually, if I add a lot of ingredients to a burger, it is scrollable because we configured it to
Teraz, gdybym mia duo skadnikw do burgera, mona go przewija, poniewa tak go
be,
skonfigurowalimy.
so the price should probably display it above the build controls, let's say.
Tak wic cena powinna prawdopodobnie wywietla si powyej elementw sterujcych budow, powiedzmy.
So in the build controls here, besides outputting the controls,
Tak wic kontrola zbiorcza tutaj oprcz wyprowadzania kontroli.
I want to show the burger price and we can simply use a paragraph here where we say current price colon
Chc pokaza cen burgera i moemy po prostu uy akapitu, w ktrym mwimy o biecej wartoci dwukropka.
and then I expect to get the price passed in with props.
A potem spodziewam si, e cena zostanie przekazana za pomoc rekwizytw.
So props.price, something like that.
Cena tego propa jest taka.
Now the price is calculated in the burger builder container,
Teraz cena jest obliczana w pojemniku Bergere Boulder.
here we have the total price state. So I want to pass this price to my build controls then because that is where
Tutaj mamy stan cakowitej ceny, aby przekaza t cen do kontrolowanej S10, poniewa
I just added the usage of that property.
wanie tam dodaem uycie tej waciwoci.
So let's add the price property,
Dodajmy wic waciwo ceny.
the name I just picked in build controls and pass this.state.totalPrice,
Nazwa, ktr wanie wybraem w sterowaniu budow i przekazuj t cakowit cen stanu.
make sure to save all files and let's have a look,
Pamitaj, aby zapisa wszystkie folletty i spjrzmy.
we see the current price here
Widzimy obecn cen tutaj.
and if I add ingredients, you see this price increases, here however we get it back with decimal numbers
A jeli dodaj skadniki, zobaczysz, e cena ronie tutaj, ale wracamy z liczbami dziesitnymi
in javascript so we should fix this and maybe we also want to print that in
w javascript, wic powinnimy to naprawi i moe wszyscy chcemy to wydrukowa.
well, emphasized.
Dobrze podkrelone.
So what we can do in the build controls for one, let's wrap this in a strong tag,
To, co moemy zrobi w artykule w sterowaniu budowaniem dla tego, ktry jest opakowany, znajduje si w silnym tagu.
the price so that is basically with font-weight
Cena tak, aby to w zasadzie z wag czcionki.
bold and let's fix it by fixing this price here.
Bold i naprawmy to, ustalajc tutaj t cen.
Now for that, price needs to be a number but thankfully it is,
Teraz, gdy ta cena musi by liczb, ale na szczcie tak jest.
so now we can call toFixed on it and fix it to two decimal places.
Teraz moemy zadzwoni, aby naprawi i naprawi go z dokadnoci do dwch miejsc po przecinku.
Let's save this
Zapiszmy to.
and now we see four
A teraz widzimy cztery.
and if I start adding, you see the price goes up. I guess we built a quite affordable burger here which
A jeli zaczynam dodawa Widzisz, cena idzie w gr Chyba ludzie do cakiem niedrogiego hamburgera
looks really delicious.
tutaj, ktry wyglda naprawd pysznie.
So with that, the burger builder is actually in pretty good shape.
Tak wic budowniczy burger jest w cakiem dobrej formie.
The check out button is missing but that's something I will add in a second
Brak przycisku check out, ale to co, co dodam w cigu sekundy.
and thereafter we need to take care about all that navigation which is hidden here at the top.
A potem musimy zadba o ca t nawigacj, ktra uderza tu na grze.